Sanket Amin



amin.sanket.sa@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/thesanketamin



8460902001



https://sanketamin.me/

Summary

Currently pursuing B-Tech (EC) from Birla Vishvakarma Mahavidyalaya (BVM).

I am passionate of programming, particularly in language C++, Python, OOP.

Also interested in embedded system and IoT. Have worked on software such as Keil, MATLAB, Proteus, Arduino IDE, Xilinx and many more.

I've done my 2nd year summer internship from Reliable Electronics, which is based in Anand, Gujarat. During my academic career of till now, I've worked on various mini projects, assigned by the college, which includes Automatic Ignition Locking System, Smart Temperature Controlled System, Commercial and Residential Smart Parking System.

Experience

Intern

Reliable Electronics

May 2021 - Jun 2021 (2 months)

During this period of internship, I had undergone training on electronic circuit designing tool & had also worked on various simulation & hardware part. I had done enhanced electronics components creation, circuit designing and fault finding of circuit, time management and documentation work skills. I also had hands on experience on software such as Proteus Design Suit and Arduino IDE and thus creating simulation project in the same.

***IEEE SB Member**

IEEE BVM SB

Mar 2019 - Dec 2020 (1 year 10 months)

Education



😡 Birla Vishvakarma Mahavidyalaya

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Electrical, Electronics and Communications Engineering

Aug 2019 - May 2023



Zen School

Secondary and Higher School, Higher Education/Higher Education Administration Mar 2007 - Mar 2019

I have completed my schooling of 1st to 12th class from Zen School, throughout CSBE medium.

Licenses & Certifications

- Student Excellence & Learning Program (SELP) National Project Implementation Unit India
- Introduction to the Internet of Things and Embedded Systems Coursera JAZTLSYF5E8P
- Introduction to Programming Using Python Udemy UC-da5f77a3-0468-487a-a493-6f7b13973a71
- Python Programming LinkedIn AdlKVbBVihOtHObhtkusY683cpcT

Skills

Python (Programming Language) • C++ • HTML • Java • MySQL • Cybersecurity • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • SQL • C (Programming Language) • MATLAB

Honors & Awards

Virtual Hackathon 2019 - IEEE PES SB Chapter (SEC)
Aug 2019